Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing That
surely someday we just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver With our
dreaming hand Let's head on towards
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your
hands up Sing about what
you are dreaming Always
stand up Raise up the flag
that you believe in Gotta
keep up We'll get past
everyone that's in our way
Let's head on never stopping
Only look up Keep your head up way up
high Always step up If waves are rough,
jump to the sky Never give up Our wishes,
they will come together And
lead us on for the future
We drift on riding the
waves Towards another
shore day by day There are many meetings,
many goodbyes Underneath the flag we fly
I'll remember the pain within I'll keep
it in my heart forever And never take it
lightly But I won't surrender This freedom
I will keep in mind I'll keep holding on,
never stop it Now everybody
lift your hands up Sing
about what you are dreaming
Always stand up Raise
up the flag that you believe
in Gotta keep up We'll
get past everyone that's
in our way Let's head on,
never stop it
Only look up Keep your head up, way up
high Always step up If brains are up,
jump to the sky Never give up Our wishes,
they will come together And
lead us on for the future
Hands up
A member of the Seven
Warlords Trafalgar Law
A powerful rookie who's butted heads with
the world government countless times,
Straw Hat Luffy.
His Gourmet, the demon child,
Nico Robin, is with him as well.
The others appear to be Smoker
and Tashigi from the Navy.
The question is, how did Caesar
get his hands on so many big shots?
Indeed.
Them again.
So that's where they ended up.
Straw Hat huh little punk finally got
off his ass fancy that I've seen enough.
This won't end well and I prefer more
hands-on approach
to violence huh yeah.
Same I wonder what Straw Hat is
doing with a warlord though probably.
Trafalgar's idea and here
I thought he'd lost his
spine when he sold out to
the government that bastard.
He's up to something big mark my
words and Straw Hats in on it.
Won't do us any good worrying about them.
Keep your eyes on our team fine.
Just don't pick a fight.
Okay.
I know shut up
It's been a long time kid
we just got here man
you don't have to look
so freaked out already
what the hell is this do
you have a death wish nobody smashes up my
hideout and gets away with
it we tried to stop him
please don't be angry
i was just making sure
you didn't have any
snipers waiting to pick me
off when your enemy
invites you to his base you
gotta take proper
precautions know what i mean
I told you.
Scratchman is a pain in the ass.
We shouldn't have invited
him in the first place.
He's strong.
I'm sure he'll be worth the trouble.
Actually, screw this meeting.
I'm gonna kill both of you right now!
See?
You do want me dead.
Well, bring it on.
I'm ready.
You think you can get with this, Phil?
This is insane.
I won't let you waste my time.
Hawkins, wait!
Just hear us out!
Everyone calm down and shut the hell up
we didn't call you here to pick a fight.
We want to form an alliance
with both of your crews.
Let's try this again like
civilized men this time.
Time for a comeback huh
yeah somebody's got to
clean this mess up we've
wasted enough time here.
I've got a couple of ideas,
but if anyone here can burn
things, that might speed this up.
Franky can make fire.
Laser beams, too. Oh, hey!
I should have thought of that sooner.
Why don't you melt our chains off?
It's not that easy.
I need both hands to
shoot my radical beam.
But there's one thing I can do.
Straight from my butt. Coo-da-boo!
Look, can you set fire to
that Navy ship down there?
You ask, and I deliver, brother.
Just sit back and watch me work.
Franky!
Fireball!
What the hell was that? Run away!
Hmm?
What is that
pacifista-looking dance up to?
Throwing a temper tantrum
from inside his cage
absurd but take heart
my dear mechanical man.
When you're dead I'll
put your body to good use
in my lab I can't see the
cage hope they're safe.
Captain don't die don't
let the smoke get you
smoky yeah I think the
smoke guy's gonna be fine.
Are you happy now Trafalgar you didn't
think this one through too well did you.
You're the one who burned the ship only
cuz you asked me to
now
that Caesar's Video
transponder snails can't
see us we'll have a
minute before he figures
Out what's going on you
better get this plan moving quick though I
don't get it how'd you
Get those chains off their
sea prism stone right
no mine were ordinary
chains though no one
knew That nothing here my
power can't take care
of think for a second
I've been on the island
for Months now I was
prepared for something
like this to happen as
soon as I noticed the
sea prism chains Around
the lab I started
replacing them with normal
chains I could easily
switch out with my Power
obviously I couldn't trust
Caesar so this is no surprise
you're
still
in a cage you moron.
I'm free, I'm free.
Oh, that's right.
We have some other
distinguished guests here.
You've learned a bit too much.
You're both at my mercy.
What should I do, huh?
Stop wasting our time,
dammit You want to kill us?
Just do it already
Your marine stop screaming
like a school girl.
Get up, dammit.
Just get the chains off, please.
Get us out of here and
I'll do anything you say.
Don't you have any pride?
A marine would rather die than
beg a pirate for their life.
I don't care.
We have other things to
worry about and other people.
If we get killed over our stupid pride,
then all of our men are as good as dead.
The Vice Admiral will...
I mean Vergo.
We'll continue to cover
up what's happening here.
You should listen to her.
She's right.
Frankly, I have no obligation to
spare your life, White Hunter.
However, if you make it out of
here and ruin Vergo's reputation,
then that suits my ends.
One catch.
I need you to forget all you
heard about me and Joker.
That's not a petty request.
It's a condition.
You give me that, and
I give you your life.
Wonder what's going on down there.
All right! No more waiting.
I'm gonna go sleep.
Stop that.
Hey, what are you doing?
Idiot doesn't even know the plan. Yeah.
Should have kept him chained up then.
How are we supposed to get inside here?
Quick question.
Brother, do you need my help?
Because I'd really rather
go check up on the sun.
Do what you want.
And what's that look for?
Run away!
I'm over feverishly up out of my legs.
It draws closer still.
Sadly, it seems the dragon is much
more adept in running than we are.
We gotta catch up so
we can fly out of here.
I can't keep up.
Just a little bit longer, Samji.
I don't know if I can.
Nami isn't built for this kind of abuse.
Her lungs can't take anymore.
Dammit, my chest is
really starting to hurt.
Her chest.
I mean...
Huh?
Bombs!
I caught it!
If it's that easy, you should
have done it in the first place!
I feel like I'm coming down with
something just looking at that thing.
Hang in there a little longer, Brownie.
I know you're injured, so thank
you for carrying us like this.
You guys are bite-sized compared to me.
This is nothing.
And besides, I gotta get back
and rescue my men either way.
Yeah, we gotta help those kids, too.
I just hope we can make it there
before they eat that candy.
Look down.
Do you see that?
See?
We're not the only ones
running from the gas.
A dragon?
Look!
The shutter's opening!
I don't know how the hell they got the
thing open, but this is a big emergency!
Did some moron in here
touch the lever?! Crap!
Those G5 guys are pouring in!
What's going on here?!
That's...
that's Vice Admiral Smoker!
The Warlord Trafalgar Law!
And the famous pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
How are they here?
I thought the Master had them locked up!
We made it.
All of our men are inside.
All right.
Let's see if we can get my heart back.
This is gonna be awesome!
I'm working with pirates. How shameful.
What's that in front of the poison?
Oh, no, wait!
No, no, no, no, no!
Are you kidding me?! No!
We're so close! Have mercy!
We're all about to die out here!
We're dead after all that!
And we tried so hard too!
Boy, I seem to be giving
up the ghost already.
I'll have company soon.
Yo, get him on!
Think you can cut through iron?
Most certainly!
Have no fear!
Let's keep up the pace!
You want me to dash my
friends out on that wall?
Now there's a giant hole in the shotter!
Hey guys, I'm here too!
What's up?
Everyone's here?
Okay, it's time to party!
What did you just do?
Are you trying to kill us all?
Well, we made it in.
But that means the gas can come in, too!
What the hell are you idiots thinking?
We're all gonna die with you now!
Hurry!
Let's plug up that hole!
Come on, guys!
We've got to be quick!
Come on, come on!
Hello, Doomsday.
Not an inch of the
island remains habitable.
The gas is still as thick
as pea soup out here.
One foot out the door would undoubtedly
mean a swift and painful death.
Well, how does it look?
Leak and ravage like
something from a nightmare.
It's truly terrifying. You're terrifying!
Good.
Nothing about this is good!
We were safe here till you
came barging through the wall!
It didn't even help us plug up the hole!
You guys have pissed us
off one too many times.
Play nice, Straw Hats, or
we'll blow your heads off.
You too, Brownbeard.
It's not like we can go back outside.
We're cornered.
No running now.
Good thing we don't need to run then.
Well, we should have seen this coming.
How cute they think they're threatening.
They said my name they've heard of me
hey things are heating up down there?
Listen you two will not
interfere with me or
Straw Hat and his crew
understood all right!
Look, it's him!
Hey, Traffy!
Now's our chance!
Hurry, do your thing!
Switch us back!
No, don't listen to her! We're okay!
Oh no!
The dream is over now!
I'm back!
Wait a second...
I think...
Sanji?
Why am I wearing a different coat?
Did you take off my clothes?
Wait, hold on.
I can explain.
Explain. Explore. Explain.
Explore.
What the hell?
My body hurts.
And from a whole lot more than one punch.
Yeah, that was Caesar.
Yeah, he beat Nami pretty
badly, actually. What?
I'm so glad he hurt my body and not hers.
You truly are a prince among men!
Alright, everybody, shut
up and listen to me!
No!
As you may have noticed, the whole
island is filled with poison gas.
But there is a way out.
There's a passage that's
completely enclosed.
There is a tall door marked R-66.
That is the entrance to the
passage that leads to the sea.
I'd rather not massacre everybody here.
So, here's the deal.
You have two hours to find your way out,
and if not, I can't guarantee your safety.
Is something gonna happen to the lab?
Depends on how things turn out.
For right now, I have
to do what I have to do.
All right.
Robin, could you do me a favor?
Yes, Luffy.
G-5!
Smokey!
There are prisoners here.
Young children who were
kidnapped two years ago.
Your mission is to retrieve them.
Then find the door that's labeled R-66.
If what law told us was true,
that passage leads to a harbor.
Steal a ship and we'll
kiss Punk Hazard goodbye.
Oh, hell yeah!
I'm ready to get out of here!
The children, yeah.
All right, everyone.
Let's split up and look for those kids.
When we find them, we need to get them
to building R, door R66. I'll do that.
Hold on, Zoro.
You can't go alone. Huh?
Not much longer, Momonosuke.
I will save you, I swear it.
That can be arranged.
I'll see to it for you. Thanks. Now then.
Better get ready, Caesar,
because I'm coming for you.
This time, I won't pass out.
First I'll kick your
ass, then I'll kidnap it
Tshiki, until I get back I'm leaving
you in charge of the men, understood?
Get back?
But where are you going, Smoker?
There go, that's who you're after, right?
I can't let him get away
The law won't see that traitor punished
the way he deserves to be You know that
i have to handle it myself
nobody screws around
with my navy wait at
least take me with you sir
i can help you know how strong Brook is if
something were to happen
to you then our men
would need someone to look after them go
toshiki help those fools
escape the children too
good luck vice admiral
huh is it true luffy
really got beaten by that
maniac caesar it's true
and there was even a
little bit of suffocation
thrown into the mix
for good measure manipulates
gas and that makes
him one dangerous bastard
he sucks the oxygen
right out of the air we
let the yetis get the
drop on us now this crap
too that is so pathetic
we gave up two years
was it all for nothing
well try looking at it this way we're all
still alive aren't we maybe not for long
if we keep letting ourselves get
caught off guard we're gonna get killed
Luffy, you hear me?
Zoro?
You have got to get it together.
We're in the new world.
Steaks are high.
Just what we needed.
A kick in the ass.
Yeah, real sorry.
Won't happen again, promise.
It's Straw Hat!
Bring him down before he
can do anything stupid!
Go! Go!
Ahhhh!
Beautiful!
See? I got this!
Can you take anything seriously?
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
And here we go!